tviexpress.com 2013-01-30

# TVI EXPRESS - Privacy Policy

**Collection of Information**

TVI Express is committed to protecting the privacy and security of our website visitors and customers. Information we collect is used solely to improve our services and enhance our overall customer experience. Any information you provide will never be sold to any third parties or mass marketers.

We may collect non-personal information about the ways that visitors use the TVI Express website for tracking information, statistics, and marketing research purposes. The information we obtain allows us to review activity and how to improve our website for our customers. Visitors who use our website never need to provide personal information if they choose not to.

**How We Use Personal Information**

TVI Express may seek personal information from you to provide you with a service, place an order, or fulfill a request. We will never discuss payment information (e.g. credit card numbers) with anyone but you. TVI Express is a Direct Sales Company and as such, we may provide personal information as needed to your personal TV Express Independent Associate or Upline Sponsor for orders and Associate enrolments. All TVI Express Independent Associates must abide by this Privacy Policy.

**Website Changes and Associate Replicated Website Changes**

We may add to, modify, or delete parts of our website as needed. For security purposes, we reserve the right to add to, modify, or delete parts of Associate Replicated Websites as needed. For example: We do not allow certain claims to appear on any Associate Replicated website and may remove them for the security of the company.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive, not on our website. We may use cookies to store your Associate password so that you do not have to re-enter it continually or to remember in what language you prefer to see the website. Cookies may also allow us to research and improve our website to match your needs. We do not use cookies to research your activity on other websites. You may always decline our cookies if your browser permits. We encourage you to add http://www.tviexpress.com as a trusted site in your browser if possible and to decline cookies from all non-trusted sites.

**Security**

We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption where there is private or confidential information displayed on our website. SSL encryption ensures that your information is protected and will not be accessible by third parties. 

**Limits**

TVI Express cannot be liable for any information obtained by outside parties from your use of this website or by your activities as a TVI Express Associate. We cannot guarantee absolute privacy from any hypertext links on our website leading to other websites. We encourage that you be careful providing information to any third parties other than TVI Express.

**Acceptance of Privacy Policy**

By using this site, you agree to the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please discontinue your use of this website. TVI Express reserves the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time.
